

MY CONTACT

Phone

+32 491 50 56 42

Email

jcoddens259@gmail.com

Links

jasper-coddens.github.io

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Skills

- C#
- Python
- GIT
- Java
- JavaScript
- HTML & CSS
- Docker
- Unity
- Elixir
- SOL
- Linux

Languages

Dutch Native

English

Full professional proficiency

JASPER CODDDENS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT MYSELF

I'm Jasper Coddens, a software developer with a bachelors degree in applied computer science. My specialization is in software development, meaning I have experience making mobile apps, games, websites and more. In my education, I came in contact with plenty of technologies, so I have a broad basis to build from and develop my skills even further. Personally, I'm interested in keeping up to date with the latest technologies, gaming, skiing and running.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERNSHIP AT MELEXIS JAPAN Oct 2023 – Jan 2024

I did an international internship for Melexis in their Japan office. I worked on a project involving React, Google App Engine, Gitlab CI, Terraform and more.

RETAIL WORKER AT VAUDE STORE LEUVEN Jul 2023 — Sep 2023

As a retail worker, I interacted regularly with customers and was able to improve my people skills dramatically. This meant that my team cooperation improved quite substantially.

RINDUSTRIAL WORKER AT CDM STRAVITEC Jul 2020 — Aug 2020

Worked for 1 month creating isolation materials in an industrial environment as a job student at CDM Stravitec.

ASSISTANT ENGINEER AT EXPERIMENTAL JETSET Oct 2018 — Oct 2018

Processed datasets for machine learning at Experimental Jetset for Youca action day. This is an initiative to work one day, and your pay is given to charity.

EDUCATION

Sep 2020 BSC APPLIED COMPUTER SCIENCE

Feb 2024 UCLL campus proximus, Haasrode, Belgium

Sep 2013 SECUNDARY EDUCATION

Jul 2019 GO! Atheneum De Ring, Leuven, Belgium